[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61a4e5925221257dd240e0da"
  },
  "id_questionnaire": {
    "$oid": "61a4a9bfcd0ecec9ff6a7d8b"
  },
  "id_user": {
    "$oid": "61a4abc7cd0ecec9ff6a7dac"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "question": "Q1",
      "goodAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "m",
      "question": "Q2"
    },
    {
      "answer": "7",
      "question": "Q3",
      "goodAnswer": "7"
    }
  ],
  "note": 2,
  "noteTotal": 3,
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61a62e5661441e487ccae4bd"
  },
  "id_questionnaire": {
    "$oid": "61a4a9bfcd0ecec9ff6a7d8b"
  },
  "id_user": {
    "$oid": "61a4abc7cd0ecec9ff6a7dac"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "7",
      "question": "Q3",
      "goodAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "answer": "3",
      "question": "Q1",
      "goodAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "n",
      "question": "Q2"
    }
  ],
  "note": 0,
  "noteTotal": 3,
  "statut": "A corriger",
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61a79fca262b7426b2150af7"
  },
  "id_questionnaire": {
    "$oid": "61a774047be00877002c5450"
  },
  "id_user": {
    "$oid": "61a4abc7cd0ecec9ff6a7dac"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "l",
      "question": "Q2"
    },
    {
      "answer": "7",
      "question": "Q3",
      "goodAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "question": "Q1",
      "goodAnswer": "1"
    }
  ],
  "note": 0,
  "noteTotal": 3,
  "statut": "A corriger",
  "datePassage": {
    "$date": "2021-12-01T16:16:03.456Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61a7a11a262b7426b2150b41"
  },
  "id_questionnaire": {
    "$oid": "61a774047be00877002c5450"
  },
  "id_user": {
    "$oid": "61a4abc7cd0ecec9ff6a7dac"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "c",
      "question": "Q2"
    },
    {
      "answer": "7",
      "question": "Q3",
      "goodAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "answer": "3",
      "question": "Q1",
      "goodAnswer": "1"
    }
  ],
  "note": 0,
  "noteTotal": 3,
  "statut": "A corriger",
  "datePassage": {
    "$date": "2021-01-10T23:00:00Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61af864549d37924e98542f0"
  },
  "id_questionnaire": {
    "$oid": "61a4a9bfcd0ecec9ff6a7d8b"
  },
  "id_user": {
    "$oid": "61a4abc7cd0ecec9ff6a7dac"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "3",
      "question": "Q1",
      "goodAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "14",
      "question": "Q3",
      "goodAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "answer": "n",
      "question": "Q2"
    }
  ],
  "note": 0,
  "noteTotal": 3,
  "statut": "A corriger",
  "datePassage": {
    "$date": "2021-12-07T16:05:19.476Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "61af8afe49d37924e98543c1"
  },
  "id_questionnaire": {
    "$oid": "61af8abf49d37924e98543b4"
  },
  "id_user": {
    "$oid": "61af8a6a49d37924e985439f"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "nous",
      "question": "Qui?",
      "goodAnswer": "nous"
    }
  ],
  "note": 2,
  "noteTotal": 2,
  "datePassage": {
    "$date": "2021-12-07T16:25:27.977Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
}]